Robin Rakowski

100 D Royal Oak Drive, Bel Air, MD 21015 • (443) 655-2448 • robin.tselepis@gmail.com

Summary

Motivated Sales Associate with five years sales experience. Independent worker with high energy and great communication skills. Reliable and friendly professional who can work with little oversight and collaborate in team environments. Mobile phone specialist.

Highlights

- Service-minded
- Product knowledge
- Order processing
- Expertise in shrink control
- Motivated seller
- · Persuasive communicator
- Accurate and efficient
- Multi-tasker

Experience

SALES REPRESENTATIVE / REPAIR LIAISON Jared Jewelry Boutique - White Marsh, MD

May 2015 - Present

- Attaining and surpassing commission-based sales goals.
- Cleaning and analyzing jewelry for repairs.
- Handling and processing paperwork for the repair division.

SALES REPRESENTATIVE AT&T Wireless - Bel Air, MD

Oct. 2010 - May 2015

- Maintain constant presence on sales floor to address customer needs.
- Recommend appropriate items and direct or lead customers to selections.
- Consistently reach or surpass monthly sales objectives as established by management.
- Maintain complete, up-to-date knowledge of wireless technology plus all AT&T products and services.
- Demystify communications technology for non-tech savvy customers.

BANK TELLER Oct. 2008 - Oct. 2010 Aberdeen Proving Ground Federal Credit Union - Abingdon, MD

- Handle bank transactions for APGFCU customers.
- Refer Credit Union products and services when appropriate.
- Maintain a cash drawer with accuracy.
- Responsibile for opening and closing branch when needed.

RECEPTIONIST May 2006 - Oct. 2008

A-1 Accounting, Inc. - Havre de Grace, MD

- Arrange appointments for all CPAs and tax professionals.
- Assist with processing financial materials.
- Prepare materials for client meetings.
- Greet clients and direct phone calls.

Education